Guide to the Feminist Women's Health Center Records, 1973-2003 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1977-2003, (23 boxes)
  - General Subject Files, 1977-2003, (17 boxes)
    - American Life League (ALL) News, 1991 (Box 60)
    - ALL News, 1990 (Box 60)
    - ALL News, 1989 (Box 60)
    - ALL News, 1988 (Box 60)
    - About issues, 1988-1992 (Box 60)
    - Clinic articles, 1981 (Box 60)
    - Incontinence program (Box 60)
    - NAF seminar (medical abortion), 1996 (Box 60)
    - NAF seminar (clinical policy guidelines), 1996 (Box 60)
    - Senior Staff Meeting (Box 61)
    - Breast self exam (BSE) information (Box 61)
    - Jan Douglass and Clara Axam, 1993 (Box 61)
    - AIDS organizations (Box 61)
    - Diversity (Box 61)
    - Tour (ME), 1990 Apr (Box 61)
    - Spain reports, 1989 Nov, 1990 Jul (Box 61)
    - Carol Downer trip report, 1989 Feb (Box 61)
    - Post-APHA trip, 1991 (Box 61)
    - Self-help tour (Box 61)
    - Williams, Mitchell (Box 61)
    - Paris trip report for FWHC's (Box 61)
    - Reproductive health technologies project (Box 61)
    - Rey, Jacqueline articles (Box 61)
    - Rotation to Federation office (Box 61)
    - Letter to German women (Box 61)
    - Hoechst (Box 61)
    - Hoechst product (Box 61)
    - RU-486 questionnaire (Box 61)
    - E. Aubeny article (Box 61)
    - Georgia Childcare Advocacy Coalition (Box 61)
    - RU-486 articles (Box 61)
    - Grimes article- RU-486 (Box 61)
    - RU-486 (Box 61)
    - Politics of caring (Box 61)
    - Meredith Turshen articles (Box 61)
    - RU-486, 1992 (Box 61)
    - Second trimester abortion risk management seminar, 1992 (Box 61)
    - RU-486, 1993 Mar (Box 62)
    - Thank you letters- France (Box 62)
    - RU-486- Newsweek (Box 62)
    - RU-486- NY Times articles (Box 62)
    - Silent Scream articles from MFPF (Box 62)
    - Parental notice- Atlanta media (Box 62)
    - Training of trainers (Box 62)
    - Participatory clinic (Box 62)
    - FWHC history/articles (Box 62)
    - Atlanta Abortion Rights Movement (ARM) meeting notes (Box 62)
    - ACOG action (Box 62)
    - ME coverage, (4 folders) (Box 62)
    - Political education (PE), 1980 (Box 62)
    - PE, 1982 (Box 62)
    - Anti-abortion incidents, 1992 Mar (Box 62)
    - FWHC's Jan Thomas report (Box 62)
    - Fed conference (Box 62)
    - Abortion as a civil rights issue (Box 62)
    - Jan and Clara- Diversity/restructure (Box 62)
    - City council resolution on injunction (Box 62)
    - FWHC personnel policies (Box 62)
    - Federation (Box 63)
    - Press phone list (Box 63)
    - Abortion handbook, pre-1973 (Box 63)
    - Abortion symposium, 1974 (Box 63)
    - Abortion task force (Box 63)
    - Building hit/driver, 1993 Nov (Box 63)
    - Property damage, 1993 Jun (Box 63)
    - HC renovations (Box 63)
    - Legislator's handbook (Box 63)
    - Legislative information- general (Box 63)
    - Nurse protocol dispensing bill (Box 63)
    - Fetal disposal bill (Box 63)
    - AIDS bill HB1281 (Box 63)
    - Georgia AIDS Legislative Coalition (Box 63)
    - Fetal indications program (Box 63)
    - Mammography (Box 63)
    - Georgia abortion providers (Box 63)
    - Parental notification bill - Ga. (Box 63)
    - Parental notification, 1988 (Box 63)
    - Parental notification implementation (Box 63)
    - Parental notification- press coverage (Box 63)
    - Parental notification law (Box 63)
    - Parental notification- media points (Box 63)
    - Parental notification- motion for stay (Box 63)
    - Parental notification- FWHC screening forms (Box 63)
    - Parental notification training manual- FWHC (Box 63)
    - Thomas/Hill hearing (Box 63)
    - Reproductive rights update, 1991 (Box 63)
    - Reproductive freedom update, 1992 (Box 63)
    - Reproductive rights update, 1990-1991 (Box 64)
    - Director's meeting, 1993 (Box 64)
    - Parental notification (Box 64)
    - Disaster plan (Box 64)
    - Floor plan (Box 64)
    - Our Daughters' Decisions (Box 64)
    - Parental notification laws- ACLU booklet (Box 64)
    - PPFA v. National Park Service (Box 64)
    - Georgia abortion providers, 1992 (Box 64)
    - Georgia Abortion Providers Association (Box 64)
    - Abortion-related legislation, 1990 (Box 64)
    - Georgia abortion providers (Box 64)
    - Staff training/continuing education, 1993-1996 (Box 64)
    - Continuing education, 2000 (Box 64)
    - Continuing education, 2002 (Box 64)
    - Abortion clinic directory (Box 64)
    - Abortion- medical statistics (Box 65)
    - Abortion clinic- how to start (Box 65)
    - First trimester technique- abortion clinic setting (Box 65)
    - Abortion- Hyde Amendment (Box 65)
    - Abortion - legal, (4 folders) (Box 65)
    - Abortion rights (Box 65)
    - Adoption (Box 65)
    - Alcoholism (Box 65)
    - Amniocentesis (Box 65)
    - Anatomy (Box 65)
    - Anemia (Box 65)
    - Anti-abortion forces (Box 65)
    - Astrological birth control (Box 65)
    - Battered wives (Box 65)
    - Benedictin (Box 65)
    - Birth control experimentation (Box 65)
    - Birth control training (Box 65)
    - Blood pressure info (Box 66)
    - Bradley Method (Box 66)
    - Breast cancer (Box 66)
    - Breast feeding (Box 66)
    - Breast self-exam (Box 66)
    - Breast surgery (Box 66)
    - C-section (Box 66)
    - Cancer- general (Box 66)
    - Carasa (Box 66)
    - Cervical cancer (Box 66)
    - Cervical cap (Box 66)
    - Cervix (Box 66)
    - Childbirth (Box 66)
    - Childbirth questionnaire (Box 66)
    - Child care (Box 66)
    - Chiropractic (Box 66)
    - Contraceptive technology (Box 66)
    - Consciousness-raising (CR) groups (Box 66)
    - Counseling- bill to regulate (Box 66)
    - Crabs (Box 66)
    - Depo-Provera (Box 66)
    - Diethylstilbesterol (DES) (Box 66)
    - Diaphragm (Box 66)
    - Drug industry (Box 66)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 66)
    - Physicians for Reproductive Choice and Health (PRCH): Manual Vacuum Aspiration, 2000 (CD included) (Box 66)
    - PRCH: Medical Abortion presentation packet (Box 67)
    - Coalition for Abortion and Reproductive Equality, 1993 Jun 10 (Box 67)
    - Feminist therapy in the 90s, 1995-1996 (Box 67)
    - Women's resource guide, 1996 (Box 67)
    - Macon press coverage, 1991-1993 (Box 67)
    - Macon editorials, 1992 (Box 67)
    - Macon sex Education, 1992 Apr 30 (Box 67)
    - Abortion care/Well-Woman care, (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - Creating Excellence: abortion care for the 21st century, 1999 Apr 25-28 (Box 67)
    - The Population Council- Mifepristone, 1997 (Box 67)
    - Well-Woman project (Box 67)
    - Communicating across boundaries (Box 67)
    - ACE outpatient treatment and day hospital (Box 67)
    - HIV/AIDS (Box 68)
    - FWHC capital campaign/fundraising, 2000 (Box 68)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 68)
    - Global Campaign for Microbicides event, 2001 (Box 68)
    - Grassroots special events fundraising training event, 2003 (Box 68)
    - Stand Up for Choice event, 2002 (Box 68)
    - Women's assembly, 1998 (Box 68)
    - The Quest for Excellence in Reproductive Health, 1997 Oct 30-31 (Box 68)
    - The Spotlight Campaign event, 2000 (Box 68)
    - Georgia Women's Movement project (Box 68)
    - Between Us: A Women's Caucus on Girls, 1999 Mar 12 (Box 68)
    - Global Lens on Child Trafficking, 2001 May 30 (Box 68)
    - Young Women's Leadership project (Box 68)
    - Medical abortion, (2 folders) (Box 68)
    - FWHC publications, 1998-2002 (Box 68)
    - Women Aware project T-shirt (Box 68)
    - FWHC T-shirt (Box 69)
    - Miscellaneous articles (Box 69)
    - Various newsletters/periodicals, (5 folders) (Box 69)
    - NAF, 1996 (Box 69)
    - Clippings (Box 70)
    - Georgia Campaign for Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention, 1997 Jan 26-29, (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Reproductive Freedom News, Center for Reproductive Law and Policy, 1994-1998, (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Translators (Box 70)
    - Georgia Women's Resource Project (Box 70)
    - Research guidelines (Box 70)
    - Rape (Box 70)
    - NAF (Box 70)
    - Independent Adoption Center (Box 70)
    - Power control (Box 70)
    - HIV program (Box 70)
    - Atlanta Pro-Choice Action Committee (Box 70)
    - Battering (Box 70)
    - Adolescents (Box 70)
    - Chrysalis Project (Box 70)
    - FWHC- History (Box 70)
    - Face-to-Face (Box 70)
    - Armenian Women (Box 71)
    - Somalia/Sudan (Box 71)
    - NAF- World Vision of Choice (Box 71)
    - Cultural resources (Box 71)
    - Memoranda, 1999-2001 (Box 71)
    - Adolescent pregnancy (Box 71)
    - Treating culturally diverse patients, (2 folders) (Box 71)
    - Media, press list (Box 71)
    - Mary Doe article (Box 71)
    - Abortion status around the world, family planning perspectives, 1990 (Box 71)
    - OR Lawsuit (Box 71)
    - Women's AIDS Prevention Project, Centers for Disease Control grant (Box 71)
    - "How to Start a Women-Controlled Abortion Clinic" (Box 71)
    - Publications and ephemera (Box 71)
    - Inner Harbour Hospitals (Box 71)
    - NAF (Box 71)
    - Emergency contraception study, 1996 (Box 71)
    - Newsletters (Box 71)
    - Psychological factors in abortion (Box 71)
- Financial Material Series, 1982-2001, (26 boxes)
  Contains records, reports, and files documenting the financial situation of the FWHC between the years 1982 and 2001. These files detail the intricacies involved in operating a women's health clinic from a financial standpoint.
  Sections of this series are arranged alphabetically and others chronologically; this reflects the original order which was preserved for the most part and also the evolving financial record-keeping manners of clinic staff.
  - General ledger, 1989 (Box 72)
  - General ledger, 1989 (Box 73)
  - General ledger, 1989 (Box 74)
  - General ledger, 1990 (Box 75)
  - General ledger, 1990 (Box 76)
  - General ledger, 1990 (Box 77)
  - General ledger, 1992 (Box 78)
  - General ledger, 1992 (Box 79)
  - General ledger, 1992 (Box 80)
  - General ledger, first quarter, 1993 (Box 81)
  - General ledger, 1994 (Box 82)
  - General ledger, 1994 (Box 83)
  - State withholding, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Form 990, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Athens property tax, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Atlanta property tax, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Federal withholding tax, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Form 990 income tax, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Federal unemployment, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Federal unemployment, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Federal withholding, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Property tax, 1984/1985 (Box 84)
  - Atlanta property tax, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Athens property tax, 1984/1985 (Box 84)
  - State withholding, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Income tax, 1977-1983, (7 folders) (Box 84)
  - Property tax, 1977-1982, (6 folders) (Box 84)
  - Athens property tax, 1983/1984 (Box 84)
  - Atlanta property tax, 1983 (Box 84)
  - 1099s sent to FWHC, 1988 (Box 84)
  - 1099s, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Federal withholding, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Federal unemployment, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Property tax, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Form 990, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Georgia withholding, 1988 (Box 84)
  - Form 990, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Report of Corporation, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Federal unemployment, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Federal withholding, 1987 (Box 84)
  - State withholding, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Property tax, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Federal unemployment, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Form 990, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Federal withholding, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Property tax (Fulton and Clarke sites), 1986 (Box 84)
  - Report of Corporation, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Miscellaneous tax information, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Athens/Macon budget, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Pre-packaged medications and other income, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Financial statements, 1991 Jun-Dec, (8 folders) (Box 85)
  - Accounts receivable weekly reports, 1989-1990 (Box 85)
  - Budget and budget-related, 1984-1991, (13 folders) (Box 85)
  - Financial statements, 1984, 1986-1989, (13 folders) (Box 86)
  - Balance sheet, 1986 Oct 31 (Box 86)
  - Income statement, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Weekly activity summary, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Property insurance, 1989-1990 (Box 86)
  - Worker's compensation, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - IRS audit attorney's report, 1990 (Box 86)
  - IRS response, 1990 (Box 86)
  - IRS audit summary, 1990 (Box 86)
  - IRS discussions, 1990 (Box 86)
  - Federation meeting re: IRS, 1990 Sept (Box 86)
  - Malpractice security trust, 1989 (Box 86)
  - Contents and liability insurance, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Insurance (Flynn St. lot), 1988 (Box 86)
  - Mag Mutual, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Promed, 1988 (Box 86)
  - IRS audit, 1988 (Box 86)
  - IRS audit correspondence (Box 86)
  - IRS questions, 1990 (Box 87)
  - IRS audit procedures (Box 87)
  - Services manual (Box 87)
  - IRS audit- extension, 1990 (Box 87)
  - Fee schedule, 1988 (Box 87)
  - IRS meeting, 1990 Oct 17 (Box 87)
  - IRS request for technical advice (Box 87)
  - Financial info (Box 87)
  - Check signers / Safe deposit (Box 87)
  - First Union Checking, 1990 (Box 87)
  - Chart of accounts, 1990 (Box 87)
  - Tax exempt letter, 1990 (Box 87)
  - Form 990, 1987, 1989 (Box 87)
  - P.I. reimbursements, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Anne Graham (Consultant) (Box 87)
  - Security, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Invoice posting, journals, 1988 (Box 87)
  - AP/AR, 1988 Dec 31 (Box 87)
  - Fund for Southern Communities (Box 87)
  - Heart Strings Grant WAPP, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Jim Anderson & Company (Box 87)
  - Mutual Security Life Insurance, 1988 (Box 87)
  - NAF (Box 87)
  - Rhode Island Hospital (Box 87)
  - Insurance (miscellaneous) (Box 87)
  - Chico FWHC loan agreements, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Fundraising letter, 1988 Dec (Box 87)
  - FWHC financials, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Form 990, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Corporation meetings minutes, 1988 (Box 87)
  - 940 and 941s, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Money market statements, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Accounts receivable, 1988 Dec 31 (Box 87)
  - Notes and mortgages payable, 1987 (Box 87)
  - IRS audit recent tax exempt letter (Box 87)
  - Brochures and literature (Box 87)
  - Record keeping for small businesses (Box 87)
  - Vandalism fundraiser letters, 1989 (Box 88)
  - Grants, 1989 (Box 88)
  - Macon News articles, 1991-1992 (Box 88)
  - Letter of Inquiry (Macon) (Box 88)
  - Proposal, Macon FWHC (Box 88)
  - Bank statements, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Clinic cash receipts, 1988, (5 folders) (Box 88)
  - Memos, staff meeting agendas (Box 88)
  - Women's Health Weekly, 1996 (Box 88)
  - Women's Health Weekly, 1995 (Box 88)
  - The Health Advocate letter, 1995 (Box 89)
  - Monthly cumulative index, 1995 (Box 89)
  - Financial statements, 1989-1991, (23 folders) (Box 89)
  - Budget analysis, 1989 Jun 30 (Box 89)
  - Monthly comparison, 1988-1989 (Box 89)
  - Financial meetings, 1989 Sept (Box 89)
  - Financial analysis, 1989 Sept (Box 89)
  - Financial projections, 1989 Jul 31 (Box 89)
  - Weekly financial reports, 1989 (Box 89)
  - Financial reports, 1989, (4 folders) (Box 89)
  - Income statements, 1989, (8 folders) (Box 89)
  - General ledger, financial statements, 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 90)
  - Workers' compensation, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 90)
  - Property insurance, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 90)
  - Building insurance, 1990-1991 (Box 90)
  - General liability accord, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 90)
  - Office package, 1989-1990 (Box 90)
  - Malpractice and general liability accord, 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 90)
  - Uncensored Party invitations, July 1991 (Box 90)
  - Transactions, 1993, (Folders 1-9 of 13) (Box 91)
  - Transactions, 1993, (Folders 10-13 of 13) (Box 92)
  - Form 990, 1990 (Box 92)
  - 1099s received, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Federal unemployment, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Georgia withholding, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Property tax, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Federal withholding, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Business license, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Georgia Abortion Rights Action League (GARAL) (Box 92)
  - Equipment sold, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Georgia withholding, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Federal withholding- FICA, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Federal unemployment, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Property tax, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Corporation registration, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Business license, 1991 (Box 92)
  - AIDS grants, 1992 (Box 92)
  - IRS correspondence, 1992 (Box 92)
  - Projected deficit, 1993 (Box 92)
  - Audit report, 2000 (Box 92)
  - Budget, 2001 (Box 92)
  - Insurance/liability (Box 92)
  - Budget profit and loss, 2001 (Box 92)
  - Proposed fees, 2001 (Box 92)
  - Clinic and community services budget/fees (Box 92)
  - Transactions, 2001 (Box 92)
  - Income/expense budget report, 2000 Oct (Box 92)
  - Income/expense budget report, 2001 Mar (Box 92)
  - Petty cash, 1984 (Box 93)
  - Cash book, 1983 (Box 93)
  - GARAL, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Georgians For Choice, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Gifts in-kind America, 1995 (Box 93)
  - General Medical Corp., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Georgia Medical Gases Inc., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Georgia Power, 1994-1995 (Box 93)
  - GynoPharma Inc., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Gynotech, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Harkness Pest Control, 1995 (Box 93)
  - HI-Q Technologies, 1995-1996 (Box 93)
  - I- miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Image Teleproducts, 1994-1995 (Box 93)
  - Info. Lab, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Info. Ventures of Atlanta, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Inglett and Stubbs, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Jewish Civic Press, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Kamedico Health Care Products Inc., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Keen and Banks, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Kinko's, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Kronos, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Lab Safety Supply, 1994 (Box 93)
  - Lease Acceptance, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Lease Card, 1995 (Box 93)
  - London International U.S. Holdings, Inc., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Mc- miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Managing Underwriters, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 93)
  - Medical Arts Press, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Medical Maintenance Consultants, Inc., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Medgyn Products, Inc., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Med X, 1994-1995 (Box 93)
  - Micro-Maintenance, Inc., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Mid-GA Courier, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Milex, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Mita Financial, 1995 (Box 94)
  - NASCO, 1995 (Box 94)
  - National Organization of Single Mothers, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Nonprofit Resource Center, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Office Depot, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Physician's Desk Reference, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Physician's Lab, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Piece of Cake, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Pitney Bowes, Inc., 1995 (Box 94)
  - Plumb Works, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Postage By Phone, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Gregory Powell Design Co., 1994 (Box 94)
  - Physician Sales and Services, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 94)
  - Q- miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 94)
  - Residential Gardening, 1995 (Box 95)
  - Riordan Protective Services, 1995 (Box 95)
  - Ryan Computer Consultant, 1995 (Box 95)
  - S&S Services, 1996 (Box 95)
  - Safeguard, 1996 (Box 95)
  - Sanifill of Georgia, Inc. 1995-1996 (Box 95)
  - Henry Schein, 1996, (4 folders) (Box 95)
  - Secretary of State of Georgia, 1996 (Box 95)
  - Southern Voice, 1995-1996 (Box 95)
  - Spic and Span, 1996 (Box 95)
  - Standard Office System, 1996 (Box 95)
  - Taylor Letter Service, 1995-1996 (Box 96)
  - TransAmerica Printing, 1995-1996 (Box 96)
  - Triad, 1995-1996 (Box 96)
  - TWG Publishing, 1996 (Box 96)
  - U- miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 96)
  - University Reporter, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Unimar, 1996 (Box 96)
  - United Health Care, 1996 (Box 96)
  - UPS, 1995-1996 (Box 96)
  - U.S. Sprint, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Wolf Camera and Video, 1996 (Box 96)
  - WRS Group, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Zinnanti Surgical Instruments, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Xytex Corp., 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - Budget, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Payroll, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Gamma Biologicals (Box 97)
  - General Medical, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Georgia Medical Gases, Inc., 1997 (Box 97)
  - Georgia Power Company, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Georgians for Choice, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Guardian, 1997 (Box 97)
  - I- miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Image Teleproducts, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Institute Paper Tech., 1997 (Box 97)
  - Iron Mountain, 1997 (Box 97)
  - J- miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Jack C. Janssen, 1997 (Box 97)
  - J.O.M. Pharmaceuticals, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Jones and Kolb, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Jewish Civic Press (Box 97)
  - Kronos, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Kaiser Permanente, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Kelly Law Firm, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Kinko's, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Lloyd, Sadd, and Anthony, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Lease Card, 1997 (Box 97)
  - AT&T, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Budget, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Budget, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 97)
  - Film benefit, 1995 Oct 17 (Box 97)
  - Worker's Compensation, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Stand Up for Choice, 1995 (Box 97)
- Legal Files Series, 1973-1990 and undated, (6 boxes)
  Contains files related to legal issues faced by the FWHC, including lawsuits and legislation which would affect women's reproductive health and the clinic.
  Original order and file names have been retained. Folders are arranged by legal issue and in smaller related groups within issue; these smaller groups were identified by the FWHC and these divisions have been retained as well.
  RESTRICTION: Some sensitive materials in this series have been relocated to the Closed Series.
  - Michelle Kamb- motion summary judgment, 1987 May 29 (Box 98)
  - Michelle Kamb, 1987-1990 (Box 98)
  - Interrogatories and responses, 1987-1988 (Box 98)
  - Keenan law firm (Box 98)
  - Kamb miscellaneous, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - Western World correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 98)
  - Complication statistics, 1986 (Box 98)
  - Abortion Complication Statistics report, 1986 (Box 98)
  - Dancy, Cheryl vs. FWHC, 1988 Jun 10 (Box 98)
  - Cheryl Dancy- complaint, 1988 (Box 98)
  - Cheryl Dancy- interrogatories, 1988 (Box 98)
  - Personal notes (Box 98)
  - Deposition- Janet Abel, 1989 Sept 15 (Box 98)
  - Deposition- Dr. Kumar, 1988 Nov 17 (Box 98)
  - Deposition- Dr. Surrender Kumar, 1989 Sept 14 (Box 98)
  - Deposition- Ann Haseltine, 1989 Sept 15 (Box 98)
  - Deposition- Nancy Sophia Richardson, 1989 Sept 14 (Box 98)
  - Deposition- Cheryl Dancy, 1989 Sept 14 (Box 98)
  - Deposition- Lynne Randall, 1990 Jun 15 (Box 98)
  - Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Correspondence from Insurance Co. (Western World Insurance Co.), 1986-1987 (Box 99)
  - Correspondence from Lynne Randall, 1986-1988 (Box 99)
  - Correspondence from Bill Zschunke, 1988 (Box 99)
  - Correspondence from Cheryl Dancy, 1986 (Box 99)
  - Lynne Randall- miscellaneous correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 99)
  - "Abortion Services in the United States," 1979-1980 (Box 99)
  - Athens newspapers, 1983 Jan (Box 99)
  - Maps (Box 99)
  - Office space- Athens, 1983 Jan (Box 99)
  - AFDC information, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Atlanta legislators, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Capitol maps (Box 99)
  - Committees of the House and Senate, 1981-1982 (Box 99)
  - Constitution- Georgia, 1976, 1982 (Box 99)
  - How a bill becomes a law (Box 99)
  - Information on legislature (Box 99)
  - Legislative terms (Box 99)
  - Map of Georgia by counties (Box 99)
  - Population of Georgia counties, 1980 (Box 99)
  - Rules of House of Representatives, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Where to obtain state information (Box 99)
  - Welfare (Box 99)
  - Members of General Assembly of Georgia, 1981-1982 (Box 99)
  - Birth center (Box 99)
  - Calendar of primary election events, 1982 (Box 99)
  - Cocktail party for legislature (Box 99)
  - ERA vote (Box 99)
  - GWPC- list of 1982 bills (Box 99)
  - Health and ecology committee, 1981-1982 (Box 99)
  - HB 300 (Box 99)
  - HB 1131 (Box 99)
  - HB 1224- feticide (Box 99)
  - Senate bill 526 (Box 99)
  - Notes (Box 99)
  - Petition for Georgia legislature (Richard), 1982 (Box 99)
  - Testimony against HB30, 1981-1982 (Box 99)
  - Georgia legislation, 1983 (Box 99)
  - Pro-choice legislation packet, 1983 (Box 99)
  - 1984 legislative session (Box 99)
  - Members of Georgia general assembly, 1984 (Box 99)
  - Medicaid audit, 1982 (Box 99)
  - Doe v. Busbee- Georgia Medicaid, 1979-1980 (Box 99)
  - Information on 1981 Mar 15 Medicaid cut-off (Box 99)
  - Medicaid card, 1981 Mar (Box 99)
  - AFWHC proposed second trimester suit (Box 100)
  - DHR- D&E battle (Box 100)
  - Georgia second trimester- reg. changes (Box 100)
  - Second trimester (Box 100)